Wen Xin told me
that you and my mother
were old acquaintances.
Wen Yan.
We've known each other for many years.
Seeing
how tragically she died on the news,
it really broke my heart.
She was such a
decisive and capable person,
yet was framed by that animal Chen Hui.
And then she was locked away
in that dark place
for so many years.
If she were still here,
Wen Group would never
have fallen to where it is today.
So I'm here to help you
to comfort her soul in heaven.
Thank you for your help.
It's just that
your offer is way too low.
Ms. Wen,
you are still too young.
I'm already being generous
with this price.
We both know that
you've talked to other investors.
Yet we are here together today,
which signifies that
I am
your optimal choice.
Alright.
Don't worry, Ms. Wen.
Now that the group is in my hands,
I will definitely make it thrive.
I hope you can keep your promise
and inject the funds to save it.
It really needs this money right now.
Money is not a problem.
I'll transfer two billion
as bridge funds to you right away
to relieve your urgent situation.
Uncle Long,
the money didn't go through.
What?
What do you mean?
I transferred the money as you instructed,
but the system shows
the funds disappeared
at the intermediary bank.
And...
the final destination marker
points to an anonymous Swiss account.
The associated information of
that account...
Tell me, who does it point to?
Tell me!
[Dearest: Episode 23]
Uncle Long,
long time no see.
I'll gladly accept your two billion.
Consider it my fee for working for you,
and my startup capital for
returning to Wen Group.
He Mu,
how dare you play me!
Uncle Long,
don't be so harsh.
The group belongs to me originally.
You were just
temporarily keeping the funds for me.
Besides, without me,
your life after you got out
wouldn't be nearly
as good as it is now, would it?
After all,
without me, there'd be no you
as you are today,
so you should thank me.
By the way,
I've decided to
change the plan.
Keeping it all for myself is
way better than splitting it with you.
Oh, and thank you for helping me handle
that silly girl Wen Jianan,
and getting her
to sign this document for me.
It saved me a lot of trouble.
He Mu,
so you and Uncle Long
are in this together.
You two joined forces to deceive me.
My dear daughter,
it's too late to realize that now.
The group
should return to its real owner.
Uncle Long,
no need to thank me for this gift.
Bye-bye.
The plan is a success.
I'll tear you to pieces!
Everyone,
search everywhere
to find that little brat for me.
I want him alive.
Look at today's high tech,
AI can swap faces in real time,
perfectly.
Even an old fox like
Uncle Long was deceived.
It's mainly because Yin Mingzhu
intercepted and froze his dirty money.
Two billion.
He was in no mood to care
if the video was real or fake.
The two billion ghost transfer,
the perfect frame-up on
He Mu's overseas account,
plus that perfectly timed
provocative video from him,
Uncle Long is now
so furious that
he wants to tear him apart.
What? The acquisition failed?
It must be Wen Jianan behind this.
She must have found out
something about me.
The plan failed.
Since his money has been wasted,
he definitely won't let me off.
Daddy, we must flee.
Uncle Long is here.
He Mu,
you ungrateful thing!
I've been loyal to you.
Now you're just leaving me here to die?
He Mu, what do you expect me to do now?
Where is he?
Uncle Long,
I... I don't know.
I really don't know.
Go after him!
Uncle Long, I... I really...
Let me tell you.
If you can't catch him, I'll ruin you.
Uncle Long,
I don't know anything.
I... I don't know anything, Uncle Long.
There's news from Yin Mingzhu.
She and the police
raided the factory where He Mu was hiding.
Did they catch him?
They only caught his assistant.
He's quite loyal,
and would rather die
than reveal He Mu's hiding place.
Loyal?
He's been with him for so many years,
so he's definitely got blood on his hands.
He knows he'll die even if he tells now,
so he might as well take a gamble.
He can run, but he can't hide forever.
This is Wen Xin's phone.
When I took her to rehab this morning,
she gave it to me.
She said she was afraid
He Mu would contact her again,
and she wouldn't be able to resist.
I thought we could take down He Mu today,
but unexpectedly,
he slipped away again.
But I know him.
He definitely won't let it go.
Now,
Wen Xin is the only card
he has left to play,
so he will definitely make a move.
He's probably trying to
use her to get to us.
So if he contacts her,
we can trace the call
to lock down his IP.
The fish took the bait.
Since Uncle Long are
so desperate to find He Mu,
why not
send him the address too.
Wen Xin,
thank goodness for you.
Once you're here,
I can hold you.
Jiang Yu and Wen Jianan
will be drawn here by you.
Right where it all began,
I will end all of this.
How perfect.
Uncle...
Uncle Long,
stop hitting me!
Let me explain!
The failure to acquire Wen Group
must be an accident.
Jiang Yu and Wen Jianan
must found out something,
so they framed me on purpose.
Two billion.
Half of my life's savings.
He Mu,
you got quite an appetite,
daring to swallow my money!
No.
You even used me as a tool
to deal with Wen Jianan,
so you could reap the benefits.
No, no, no!
Weren't you quite talkative in the video?
What video?
I don't know anything.
Swiss bank,
ending in 6688. It's yours, right?
No, it's not my card number.
I don't know anything about a Swiss bank.
I'm being framed.
It must be Jiang Yu.
It must be him.
Still arguing, huh?
They did make a move,
but you've done plenty to cross me too.
Finally,
I'll deal with them myself.
Un-uncle Long,
what the hell?
It's still hot.
Do you believe in God?
Your God can't save you either!
You broke your word
go to hell!
Longqing,
you are suspected of intentional homicide
and gang violence.
You are now under arrest.
Put down your weapons.
Good and evil will eventually be repaid.
Every sin
will be paid for.
The well-deserved commendation this time
should earn representative Yin
another promotion.
The crisis in Wen Group is over.
The lead perpetrator behind
the malicious takeover
has finally been brought to justice.
The group is back on track.
Everything
will start anew.
[Afterward, Jiang Yu and Wen Jianan voluntarily surrendered to the authorities,
confessing to their roles in setting up Wen Yanhui
to invest and resorting to vigilante justice.]
[Given their significant cooperation
in helping the police dismantle a criminal syndicate,
the court ruled as follows:]
[Jiang Yu received a three-year suspended prison sentence.
Wen Jianan was given a warning and ordered to pay civil damages.]
[Wen Xin and Wen Jianan also
voluntarily confessed to unlawfully restricting
Wen Yanhui's personal freedom.]
[For the crime of intentional harm, Wen Xin,
as the principal offender,
was sentenced to six months' controlled supervision.
Wen Jianan, as an accomplice,
received five days' detention and a fine.]